[音乐]
[MUSIC]
&gt；&gt；Douglas：编写一个Collect函数，它接受一个生成器和一个数组，然后
&gt;&gt; Douglas: Write a collect function that takes a generator and an array and
生成一个函数，该函数将收集数组中的结果。
produces a function that will collect the results in the array.
所以，我们要制造一个类似国安局的发电机。
So, we're gonna make a generator that works like the NSA.
它会监视一个功能
It's going to spy on a function and
记录函数返回的所有有趣内容，好吗？
record everything interesting that that function returns, okay?
首先，我们将设置一个空数组，Collect将在其中保存其内容，
First, we'll set up the empty array where collect is gonna keep its stuff,
然后我们将调用Collect，将任何生成器和该数组传递给它，
then we'll call collect, passing it any generator and that array,
它将返回一个生成器，它的工作方式与第一个生成器完全相同，
and it will return a generator, which will work exactly like the first generator,
除了它将记录它返回的所有内容之外
except it will record everything that it returns except for
未定义。&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：那么，
undefined. &gt;&gt; Douglas: So,
我们可以给那个发电机打几次电话，然后
we can call that generator a few times, and
然后我们可以查看数组中的内容，它将捕获这些值。
then we can look at what's in the array and it will have captured those values.
所以，这里是Collect，Collect需要一个发电机，然后
So, here is collect, collect takes a generator and
返回从生成器获取下一个值的函数的数组。
an array that returns a function that gets the next value from the generator.
如果值不是未定义的，
If the value is not undefined,
它将它推到数组的末尾，无论在哪种情况下，它都将返回值。
it pushes it on to the end of the array in either case it will return the value.
那么，谁有用的东西呢？
So, who got something that works?
[笑]这么近？
[LAUGH] So close?
有人做什么有趣的事吗？&gt；&gt；演讲者2：你能回来吗
Anybody do something interesting? &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Can you just return
array.push值，而不是将返回值放在外部
array.push value instead of having the return value outside
道格拉斯：我不记得是什么了
of the u? &gt;&gt; Douglas: I don't recall what it is
那个数组推回来了。
that array.push returns.
我认为它可能是数组的更新长度。
I think it might be an updated length of the array.
有人知道吗？&gt；&gt；扬声器3：是的，
Does anyone know? &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: Yeah,
听起来不错。&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：是的，所以
it sounds right. &gt;&gt; Douglas: Yeah, so
不幸的是，arra.push还不够聪明，无法做到这一点。
unfortunately array.push isn't smart enough to do that.
还有其他人吗，我们要去下一个吗？
Anybody else, we’re going onto the next one?
编写一个接受生成器和谓词的筛选器函数。
Write a filter function that takes a generator and a predicate.
谓词是返回布尔值TRUE或FALSE的函数，并且
A predicate is a function that returns a boolean true or false and
生成一个生成器，该生成器仅生成谓词批准的值。
produces a generator that produces only the values approved by the predicate.
因此，在本例中，我们将使用第三个函数进行过滤。
So, in this case, we're going to be filtering using the third function.
第三个函数仅在以下情况下返回TRUE
The third function will return true only if
它的参数可以被3整除，所以我们将使用它来选择
Its argument is divisible by 3, so we'll use that to select
生成器给出的序列中的因子3。
factors of 3 from the sequence given by the generator.
所以我们将把FromTo生成器设置为(0，5)，
So we'll have the fromTo generator going to (0, 5),
和第三个函数，它将返回(0，3)和
and the third function, and it will return (0, 3) and
那就是未定义。&gt；&gt；扬声器4：那么，
then undefined. &gt;&gt; Speaker 4: So,
你在问，如果我按顺序调用这个，五次，
you're asking, if I call this sequentially, five times,
我应该只得到零，三，还是未定义的？
I should only get zero, a three, or an undefined?
这些不是我应该得到的前三个结果。
Those arent the first three results I should get.
&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：这些就是结果。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: Those are the results.
&gt；&gt；扬声器4：我打了三次电话
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: I call the three times
你们自己写的结果。道格拉斯：好的，
the results yourselves write. &gt;&gt; Douglas: Okay,
让我们来看看过滤器，那么每个人都知道他们需要使用一个循环吗？
let's look at filter, so did everybody figure out they need to use a loop?
是的，这是这个的关键，所以非常好。
Yeah, that was a key to this one, so very good.
我们会讲到这一点，所以这里有一种编写过滤器的方法。
We'll get to that, so here's one way to write filter.
好吧，首先，谁有用的东西？
Well, first off, who got something that works?
非常好，所以过滤器需要一个生成器和一个谓词
Very good, so filter takes a generator and a predicate and
返回一个函数，该函数将停留在循环中，调用生成器，
returns a function, which will stay in a loop, calling the generator,
直到它获得谓词批准的值。
until it gets a value which is approved by the predicate.
在这种情况下，它将退出返回值，并且
In which case it will drop out in return the value, and
这是一种可以接受的方式。
that's an acceptable way to do it.
虽然在EF6中，我在EF6中最喜欢的新功能是
Although in EF6, my most favorite new feature in EF6 is going to
是尾递归，或者是适当的尾部调用，这会让我们这样写它。
be tail recursion, or proper tail calls, which would let us write it like this.
我们将有一个递归函数，我称之为recur，并且
We're going to have a recursive function that I'm calling recur, and
它将继续调用自己，直到谓词变为true。
it will continue to call itself until the predicate becomes true.
所以，这就是它自称的地方，而且
So, this is where it calls itself, and
这需要语言中的新功能的原因是，在ES6中，
the reason why this needs a new feature in the language Is that, in ES6,
编译器需要优化该调用。
the compiler is required to optimize that call.
所以，不是先打个电话，然后再回电话，
So, instead of doing a call and then a return,
它将跳回到recur函数。
it will do a jump back to the recur function.
因此，此函数将在同一时间运行，并且
So, this function will run in the same time and
与先前的记忆压力相同。
same memory pressure as the earlier one.
在这一点上，将不再有使用循环而不是递归的优势，
At this point, there will no longer be an advantage to using loops over recursion,
这很棒，所以我真的很期待。
and that's great, so I'm really looking forward to that.
其他人做第三种方法或者
Anybody else do a third approach or
还有别的吗？&gt；&gt；发言人3：我认为应该有
any other? &gt;&gt; Speaker 3: I think there should
成为使用[咳嗽]姿势的一种方式
be a way to use that [COUGH] pose
函数，调用函数上的函数。
function that we wrote earlier, calling a function on a function.
嗯，我们并不是真的对一个函数调用一个函数，但是
Well, we're not really calling a function on a function, but
感觉我们是。&gt；&gt；扬声器4：[听不到]因为
it feels like we are. &gt;&gt; Speaker 4: [INAUDIBLE] because
他们太习惯Python了。
they're so used to Python.
你可以，如果你回头看的话。&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：是的，混淆了
You could, if you look back to it. &gt;&gt; Douglas: Yeah, confused for
有一阵子了。
awhile there.
我实际上认为我们有太多的循环语句。
I actually think that we have too many looping statements.
如果只有我一个人，那就是一个循环，就是这样。
If it were just me, it would be a loop, and that would be it.
你知道，循环括号，所有的事情都会在里面发生。
You know, loop bracket, and everything would happen in that.
是的，因为我发现，嗯，我不再经常使用循环了。
Yeah, because I find, well, I'm not using loops much anymore.
但是，当我这样做的时候，我倾向于打破中间状态，并且
But, when I do, I tend to want to break out of the middle, and
我们有一个循环语法，它说将突破顶部，
we've got a loop syntax, which says will break out of the top,
将打破底部，但那通常不是我要去的地方。
will break out of the bottom, but that's not usually where I'm going.
如果我使用的是这种规则的循环，
If I'm using a loop that is that discipline,
我可能根本不需要使用循环。
I probably don't need to use a loop at all.
还有人吗？
Anybody else?
好的，那么我们要不要继续讲另一个？
Okay, so shall we go on to another one?
当然，有何不可？
Sure, why not?
好的，让我们再做一次，
Okay, so let's do one more,
这一次，我们将把几个函数连接在一起。
this time we're going to concatenate a couple of functions together.
因此，编写一个concat函数，它需要两个生成器和
So, write a concat function that takes two generators and
生成组合其序列的生成器。
produces a generator that combines their sequences.
所以，我们将调用concat，我们将向它传递一个生成器，即
So, we're going to call concat, we're going to pass it a generator, which is
从(2，0)到3，从(2，0)到2，这将给我们一个新的生成器，
from (2, 0) to 3, and from (2, 0) to 2, and that will give us a new generator,
这将产生序列(0，1)，(2，0)，1，然后未定义。
which will produce the sequence (0, 1), (2, 0), 1, and then undefined.
所以，这里是Concat，它需要两个生成器函数。
So, here's concat, it takes two generator functions.
它有一个变量来记住当前生成器函数是什么。
It has a variable to remember what the current generator function is.
它返回一个函数，该函数从当前生成器中获取一个值。
It returns a function which gets a value from the current generator.
如果值不是未定义的，则返回该值。
If a value is not undefined, it returns it.
否则，它将用下一个生成器替换当前的生成器，并且
Otherwise it replaces the current generator with the next generator and
从中返回一个值。
returns a value from that.
那么谁有什么东西能永远起作用呢。
So who got something that works for good.
有没有人采取不同的方法。&gt；&gt；扬声器4：[听不见]
Anyone take a different approach. &gt;&gt; Speaker 4: [INAUDIBLE]
临时发电机
temporary generator.
道格拉斯：因为。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: Because.
明年，当我们有.
Next year, when we have the...
事情，那么我想这样写。
thing, then I want to write it this way.
而我可以使用任意数量的发电机，并且
Whereas I can take any number of generators, and
我将使用我们之前编写的元素函数来帮助我执行步骤
I'm going to be using the element function that we wrote earlier to help me step
通过生成器数组，我将加载下一个生成器。
through that array of generators, and I'll just Load the next one in.
所以这就是为什么，我不是故意炫耀的，但是
So that's why, I didn't mean to show off but but
这就是为什么。&gt；&gt；发言人2：氏族是什么？
that's why. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: What are the gens?
&gt；&gt；扬声器4：让我们看看前面的
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Let's see the previous
滑动。&gt；&gt；扬声器4：层返回
slide. &gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Layer returning
代之以价值。&gt；&gt；Douglas：返回结果
gen instead of value. &gt;&gt; Douglas: returning the result of
大屠杀和所谓的简单价值，因为我认为价值它是通用汽车。
the Holocaust and call easy value as I see value it was G.M.
如果它不成功，你就叫它。
and if it doesn't succeed you're calling it a.
你知道她只是倾向于走到下一台发电机。
You know she just tends to just get to the next generator.
称它为彼此的呼唤
Call it the call that each other
相当艰难的任务一变了因为这是第一次
pretty tough assignment one changes because it's the first
时间三个原因只有一秒时间三个原因
time three cause just one second time three cause
你第三次因为你路过
your third time three cause you're passing
假设你是1到4乘以3，因为Jack Money低于5
suppose you're one to the fourth time three because Jack money gets under five
美分Janda Gentoo返回Gentoo的结果或
cents JANDA Gentoo returns a result of Gentoo or
我们有一个好的。&gt；&gt；扬声器4：尚未
we have a OK. &gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Yet
回来告诉你我期待着回来所以
to return to tell you I was expecting to return so
这也是下一件事。道格拉斯：是的。
That's as well the next stuff. &gt;&gt; Douglas: Yeah.
&gt；&gt；扬声器4：你说的是价值
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: You said value
等于Gen2。&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：对。
equals gen2. &gt;&gt; Douglas: Right.
我不可能在VF里面做那个生意。
I couldn't have done that business inside of vf.
我本来可以逆转的。&GT；&GT；扬声器4：好的，
I could have reversed it. &gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Okay,
我抓到你了。&gt；&gt；道格拉斯：是的，对。
I gotcha you now. &gt;&gt; Douglas: Yeah, right.
你觉得那样做会更清楚吗？
You think it would have been clearer doing it that way?
&gt；&gt；扬声器4：嗯，我更喜欢有一个
&gt;&gt; Speaker 4: Well, I prefer to have one
我想，还不止两个吧。&GT；&GT；道格拉斯：我会考虑的。
return than two, I guess. &gt;&gt; Douglas: I'll think about that.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：那么，当您的下一个函数
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: So, when your next function
你的&GT；&GT；道格拉斯：那么下一个。
your &gt;&gt; Douglas: Then next.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：[咳嗽]
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: [COUGH]
元素是什么？
What's element?
&gt；&gt；Douglas：element是我们编写的函数
&gt;&gt; Douglas: Element is a function we wrote
今天早上。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：是的。
this morning. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yeah.
&GT；&GT；道格拉斯：你记得这一点。
&gt;&gt; Douglas: You remember that.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：弹出，
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: It pops off,
它跳到下一个。道格拉斯：是的。
it pops off to the next. &gt;&gt; Douglas: Yeah.
&gt；&gt；扬声器2：弹出。
&gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Just pops.
&gt；&gt；Douglas：它返回来自
&gt;&gt; Douglas: It returns the next thing from
一个数组。&gt；&gt；扬声器2：不是因为弹出它。
an array. &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Not because of pop it.
道格拉斯：你应该，
&gt;&gt; Douglas: You should,
我们做了两次&GT；&GT；扬声器2：是的，就在那里。
we did it twice &gt;&gt; Speaker 2: Yeah, there it is.